<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talk to your DESFire Card</string>

    <!-- strings for prepare sun/sdm -->
    <string name="header_prepare_sdm">Prepares the tag to use the SUN/SDM feature</string>
    <string name="description_prepare_sdm">Prepares the tag by creating a new application, creating a Standard File to take the NDEF Container File (CC) and a Standard File that stores the template URL (NDEF Data File).</string>
    <string name="warning_prepare_tag">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY write to an attached tag without any further confirmation !</string>
    <string name="more_information_prepare_sdm">More Information about the application and file creations:\n
    1) The app will create a new application with applicationID 010000 and ISO application name D2760000850101,
    this is necessary for NDEF workflow. The app will have 5 AES based application keys. There are no restrictions on file and directory handling.\n
    2) In the new application a new Standard File is created with a size of 32 bytes that holds the NDEF Container File.\n
    The file number is 01 and the ISO fileId is E103h, the Communication mode is Plain,
    Access rights: Read &amp; Write key: E, CAR key: E, Read key: E, Write key: E (E means free access without any authentication)\n
    3) A second Standard File is created in the application with a sie of 256 bytes that hold the template URL for the NDEF Link record.\n
    The file number is 02 and the ISO fileId is E104h, the Communication mode is Plain,
    Access rights: Read &amp; Write key: E, CAR key: 0, Read key: E, Write key: E (E means free access without any authentication)
    </string>

    <!-- strings for activate sun/sdm -->
    <string name="header_activate_sdm">Activate the SUN feature by enabling Secure Dynamic Messaging (SDM)</string>
    <string name="description_activate_sdm">Activates the mirroring of data (UID, read counter, secret file data and MAC) in a NDEF message on tapping.\n\nThis is working on Mifare DESFire EV3 tags only.</string>
    <string name="description_activate_sdm_rg">choose your action on SUN/SDM feature</string>

    <!-- strings for read ndef content -->
    <string name="header_read_ndef_content">Read the NDEF content</string>
    <string name="description_read_ndef_content">Reads the content of the NDEF Data File (2) and displays the content in hex and string encoding</string>
    <string name="description_read_ndef_content_rg">select authenticate mode</string>

    <!-- strings for format picc -->
    <string name="header_format_picc">Format the PICC</string>
    <string name="description_format_picc">Formatting the PICC will delete all applications and files on the PICC and releases all storage space back to factory settings.\n
    The settings of the Master Application are not reset so if you changed the default Master Application Key and key settings these changes will remain.</string>
    <string name="warning_format_picc">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY FORMAT the PICC when attached without any further confirmation !\n\n
    You will loose any existing applications and files on the PICC without recovery !</string>
    <string name="more_information_format_picc">Formatting the PICC will release all storage space back to factory settings.\n
    The settings of the Master Application are not reset so if you changed the default Master Application Key and/or key settings these changes will remain.\n\n
    The app will authenticate with the DEFAULT Master Application Key first to run the format PICC command.</string>

    <!-- strings for setup test environment -->
    <string name="header_setup_test_environment">Setup a test environment</string>
    <string name="description_setup_test_environment">For testing the features of the DesfireEv3 class this activity will prepare the PICC with all necessary application and files</string>
    <string name="warning_setup_test_environment">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY run all setups when attached without any further confirmation !\n\n</string>
    <string name="more_information_setup_test_environment">More Information about the application and file creations:\n
    1) The app will FORMAT the PICC so the complete PICC memory is available.\n
    2) The app will create a new application with applicationID A1A2A3. The app will have 5 AES based application keys.
        There are no restrictions on file and directory handling (default settings).\n
    3) In the new application some files are created with these file numbers and access rights (R &amp; W 1, CAR 2, R 3, W 4):\n
    01 Standard File, 256 file size, communication mode Plain\n
    02 Standard File, 256 file size, communication mode MACed\n
    03 Standard File, 256 file size, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    04 Backup File, 32 file size, communication mode Plain\n
    05 Backup File, 32 file size, communication mode MACed\n
    06 Standard File, 32 file size, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    07 Value File, communication mode Plain\n
    08 Value File, communication mode MACed\n
    09 Value File, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    10 Linear Record file, 32 record size, 3 maximum number of records, communication mode Plain\n
    11 Linear Record file, 32 record size, 3 maximum number of records, communication mode MACed\n
    12 Linear Record file, 32 record size, 3 maximum number of records, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    13 Cyclic Record file, 32 record size, 4 maximum number of records, communication mode Plain\n
    14 Cyclic Record file, 32 record size, 4 maximum number of records, communication mode MACed\n
    15 Cyclic Record file, 32 record size, 4 maximum number of records, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    \n\nThe PICC will be formatted immediately after tapping without any further confirmation, the PICC is authenticated with DEFAULT DES Master Application KEY\n\n
    </string>

</resources>