<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talk to your DESFire Card</string>

    <!-- strings for format picc -->
    <string name="header_format_picc">Format the PICC</string>
    <string name="description_format_picc">Formatting the PICC will delete all applications and files on the PICC and releases all storage space back to factory settings.\n
    The settings of the Master Application are not reset so if you changed the default Master Application Key and key settings these changes will remain.</string>
    <string name="warning_format_picc">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY FORMAT the PICC when attached without any further confirmation !\n\n
    You will loose any existing applications and files on the PICC without recovery !</string>
    <string name="more_information_format_picc">Formatting the PICC will release all storage space back to factory settings.\n
    The settings of the Master Application are not reset so if you changed the default Master Application Key and/or key settings these changes will remain.\n\n
    The app will authenticate with the DEFAULT Master Application Key first to run the format PICC command.</string>

    <!-- strings for setup test environment -->
    <string name="header_setup_test_environment">Setup a test environment</string>
    <string name="description_setup_test_environment">For testing the features of the DesfireEv3 class this activity will prepare the PICC with all necessary application and files</string>
    <string name="warning_setup_test_environment">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY run all setups when attached without any further confirmation !\n
    This includes a FORMAT of the PICC - you will loose any existing applications and files on the PICC without recovery !</string>
    <string name="more_information_setup_test_environment">More Information about the application and file creations:\n
    1) The app will FORMAT the PICC so the complete PICC memory is available.\n
    2) The app will create a new application with applicationID A1A2A3. The app will have 5 AES based application keys.
        There are no restrictions on file and directory handling (default settings).\n
    3) In the new application some files are created with these file numbers and access rights (R &amp; W 1, CAR 2, R 3, W 4):\n
    00 Standard File, 256 file size, communication mode Plain\n
    01 Standard File, 256 file size, communication mode MACed\n
    02 Standard File, 256 file size, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    03 Backup File, 32 file size, communication mode Plain\n
    04 Backup File, 32 file size, communication mode MACed\n
    05 Standard File, 32 file size, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    06 Value File, communication mode Plain\n
    07 Value File, communication mode MACed\n
    08 Value File, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    09 Linear Record file, 32 record size, 3 maximum number of records, communication mode Plain\n
    10 Linear Record file, 32 record size, 3 maximum number of records, communication mode MACed\n
    11 Linear Record file, 32 record size, 3 maximum number of records, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    12 Cyclic Record file, 32 record size, 4 maximum number of records, communication mode Plain\n
    13 Cyclic Record file, 32 record size, 4 maximum number of records, communication mode MACed\n
    14 Cyclic Record file, 32 record size, 4 maximum number of records, communication mode Full enciphered\n
    \n\nThe PICC will be formatted immediately after tapping without any further confirmation, the PICC is authenticated with DEFAULT DES Master Application KEY\n\n
    </string>

    <!-- strings for personalizing the PICC -->
    <string name="header_personalize">Personalize the PICC</string>
    <string name="description_personalize">Changes the application keys to individual ones including the Master Application key</string>
    <string name="warning_personalize">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY run all personalizing steps when attached without any further confirmation !</string>
    <string name="more_information_personalize">More Information about the application and file creations:\n\n
    For changing the application keys from DEFAULT to CHANGED or CHANGED to DEFAULT:\n
    1) select the application with applicationID A1A2A3\n
    2) authenticate with Application Master key = key number 00 (AES DEFAULT)\n
    3) change the application keys Read &amp; Write Access, Change Access Rights, Read Access and Write Access rights (key numbers 01..04)\n
    4) change the Application Master key (key number 00)\n\n
    For changing the Master Application key from DEFAULT to CHANGED or CHANGED to DEFAULT:\n
    5) select the Master Application with applicationId 000000\n
    6) authenticate with Master Application key = key number 00 (DES DEFAULT)\n
    7) change the Master Application key value\n\n
    For changing the Master Application key from DES DEFAULT to AES DEFAULT:\n
    8) select the Master Application with applicationId 000000\n
    9) authenticate with Master Application key = key number 00 (DES DEFAULT)\n
    10) change the Master Application key from DES DEFAULT to AES DEFAULT\n\n
    Note: this is a one way option, with this app you cannot change the Master Application key back to a DES key,
    use my app MifareDesfireEv3MasterkeyToDesNFCJLib for this task.\n

    </string>

    <!-- strings for creating an application -->
    <string name="header_create_application">Create an application</string>
    <string name="description_create_application">Creates an application on the PICC with AES keys</string>
    <string name="warning_create_application">This will create an application on the PICC without any further conformation</string>
    <string name="more_information_create_application">more\n</string>

    <string name="header_create_file">he</string>
    <string name="description_create_file">des</string>
    <string name="warning_create_file">wa</string>


    <!-- strings for setup DESFire Light environment -->
    <string name="header_setup_light_environment">Setup a DESFire Light environment</string>
    <string name="description_setup_light_environment">For testing the features of the Desfire Light class this activity will prepare the PICC with all necessary application and files that are pre-installed on a DESFire Light tag</string>
    <string name="warning_setup_light_environment">WARNING: The app will IMMEDIATELY run all setups when attached without any further confirmation !\n
    This includes a FORMAT of the PICC - you will loose any existing applications and files on the PICC without recovery !</string>
    <string name="more_information_setup_light_environment">more</string>


</resources>